Hi, I'm Pete Dulcamara. I'm the author of
High Tech Heroes, Why Gen. Z is the
Last and Best Chance to Save the Planet.
And I wrote this book based on my 40
years in science and technology. You
know, I've got degrees in chemistry,
math, physics, chemical engineering. I
spent 17 years at Dow Chemical as an
executive in R&D, 17 years at
Kimberly-Clark as chief scientist.
And now I'm doing in my renaissance, not
my retirement, but my renaissance. And
it's all about helping to create
businesses that improve people's lives.
Innovation is multiplying faster than
ever.
The world 100 years ago.
The world today.
We are the first generation to.
How is our world changing?
Populations are becoming digital.
Half our life is spent online.
Less babies are being born.
People are living longer.
The world is aging.
The world is urbanizing.
Consumption is outstripping
resources. How can we
adapt?
The time has come for
exponential technologies.
Your time has come.
Humans like you are joining the
innovation revolution,
offering real solutions.
People from all generations have heard
the call,
but your generation is
special.